Ha, let's go
哈，走起
One moment, one dream
一个瞬间，一个梦想
'Cause it's that time (Ha)
因为就是这个时刻（哈）
Let's go
走起
Algeria, Argentina, Australia, Austria (Let's go)
阿尔及利亚、阿根廷、澳大利亚、奥地利（走起）
Belgium, Bosnia, Brazil (Ayy), Canada (Let's go)
比利时、波黑、巴西（Ayy）、加拿大（走起）
Cape Verde, Colombia, Croatia
佛得角、哥伦比亚、克罗地亚
Czech Republic (Yeah), Curaçao, Congo (Let's go)
捷克（Yeah）、库拉索、刚果（走起）
Ecuador, Egypt (Ha), England, France (Who we got like?)
厄瓜多尔、埃及（哈）、英格兰、法国（还有谁？）
Germany, Ghana (Come on), Haiti, Iran (Don't stop)
德国、加纳（来吧）、海地、伊朗（别停）
Iraq, Japan (Yeah), Jordan, Mexico (Come on)
伊拉克、日本（Yeah）、约旦、墨西哥（来吧）
Morocco, Netherlands (Let's go), New Zealand, Norway (Let's fight)
摩洛哥、荷兰（走起）、新西兰、挪威（拼了）
Panama, Paraguay (Let's dream), Portugal, Qatar (Let's dream)
巴拿马、巴拉圭（追梦吧）、葡萄牙、卡塔尔（追梦吧）
Saudi Arabia, Senegal (Let's win), Scotland, South Africa (Ha)
沙特阿拉伯、塞内加尔（赢下来）、苏格兰、南非（哈）
South Korea, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland
韩国、西班牙、瑞典、瑞士
Tunisia, Turkey, USA, Uzbekistan
突尼斯、土耳其、美国、乌兹别克斯坦
Uruguay, Ivory Coast
乌拉圭、科特迪瓦
Let's play football
来踢球吧
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh (Let's go)
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh（走起）
Let's go, we the champions (Ha)
走起，我们是冠军（哈）
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh (Ayy, it is the World Cup time)
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh（Ayy，世界杯时刻到了）
Let's go, we the champions (It is the World Cup time)
走起，我们是冠军（世界杯时刻到了）
'Cause this is the World Cup (World Cup)
因为这就是世界杯（世界杯）
Put your flags up in the air (In the air)
把旗帜举向空中（举向空中）
Put your hands up in the air (In the air)
把双手举向空中（举向空中）
Put your flags up, 'cause this is the World Cup (World Cup)
把旗帜举起来，因为这就是世界杯（世界杯）
Put your flags up in the air (In the air)
把旗帜举向空中（举向空中）
Put your hands up in the air (In the air)
把双手举向空中（举向空中）
Put your flags up, leave 'em there
把旗帜举起来，就让它们扬在那儿
Let's go (Let's go), let's fight (Let's fight)
走起（走起），拼了（拼了）
We up (We up), tonight (Tonight)
我们燃起来了（燃起来了），就在今夜（今夜）
Won't break (Won't break), that's right (That's right)
绝不崩溃（绝不崩溃），没错（没错）
One world (One world), unite (unite)
同一个世界（同一个世界），团结起来（团结起来）
We own it, we goin', we live for this moment
我们掌控全场，我们勇往直前，我们为这一刻而活
We told 'em, we showed 'em, we told it
我们说到做到，我们证明给他们看，我们早就放过话
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh
Let's go, we the champions (Ha)
走起，我们是冠军（哈）
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh (It is the World Cup time)
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh（世界杯时刻到了）
Let's go, we the champions (It is the World Cup time)
走起，我们是冠军（世界杯时刻到了）
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Ooh-ooh-ooh
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）Ooh-ooh-ooh
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Let's go, we the champions
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）走起，我们是冠军
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Ooh-ooh-ooh
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）Ooh-ooh-ooh
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Let's go, we the champions
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）走起，我们是冠军
We gotta rise 'til we rise to the end
我们要一路高升，直到登顶终点
We gotta dream 'til we dream 'til we win
我们要不停追梦，直到梦想成真、直到胜利
Give me the cup, the championship
把奖杯给我，把冠军给我
Told them, "I'm bringing it back to the crib"
我跟他们说过：“我要把它带回家”
To' el mundo mirando (Oh)
全世界都在注视（Oh）
Everybody gritando (Ayy)
所有人都在呐喊（Ayy）
La bola girando (Oh)
皮球飞速旋转（Oh）
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro
一，二，三，四
Let's go (Let's go), let's fight (Let's fight)
走起（走起），拼了（拼了）
We up (We up), tonight (Tonight)
我们燃起来了（燃起来了），就在今夜（今夜）
Won't break (Won't break), that's right (That's right)
绝不崩溃（绝不崩溃），没错（没错）
One world (One world), unite (Unite)
同一个世界（同一个世界），团结起来（团结起来）
We own it, we goin', we live for this moment
我们掌控全场，我们勇往直前，我们为这一刻而活
We told 'em, we showed 'em, we told it
我们说到做到，我们证明给他们看，我们早就放过话
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh
Let's go, we the champions (Ha)
走起，我们是冠军（哈）
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh (It is the World Cup time)
Oh, eh-oh, eh-oh-eh-oh（世界杯时刻到了）
Let's go, we the champions (It is the World Cup time)
走起，我们是冠军（世界杯时刻到了）
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Ooh-ooh-ooh
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）Ooh-ooh-ooh
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Let's go, we the champions
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）走起，我们是冠军
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Ooh-ooh-ooh
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）Ooh-ooh-ooh
(Na-na-na-na, na-na-na) Let's go, we the champions
（Na-na-na-na, na-na-na）走起，我们是冠军
'Cause this is the World Cup
因为这就是世界杯
Put your flags up in the air
把旗帜举向空中
Put your hands up in the air
把双手举向空中
Put your flags up 'cause this is the World Cup
把旗帜举起来，因为这就是世界杯
Put your flags up in the air
把旗帜举向空中
Put your hands up in the air
把双手举向空中
Put your flags up, leave 'em there
把旗帜举起来，就让它们扬在那儿
(Na-na-na-na-na) Ha
（Na-na-na-na-na）哈
(Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh) 2026, baby
（Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh）2026，宝贝
(Na-na-na-na-na) It's that World Cup time
（Na-na-na-na-na）世界杯时刻到了
(Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh) Stand up
（Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh）站起来
(Na-na-na-na-na) Let's go
（Na-na-na-na-na）走起
(Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh) Let's go, we the champions
（Na-na-na, ooh-ooh-ooh）走起，我们是冠军
When I step (This is the World Cup)
当我迈步（这就是世界杯）
I step with my left (This is the World Cup)
我迈出左脚（这就是世界杯）
I step with my right (This is the World Cup)
我迈出右脚（这就是世界杯）
I pump my chest (This is the World Cup)
我捶打胸膛（这就是世界杯）
I focus my mind (This is the World Cup)
我凝神聚气（这就是世界杯）
I take a breath (This is the World Cup), and wait for the ref
我深吸一口气（这就是世界杯），等待裁判哨响
This is the World Cup, put your hands up in the air
这就是世界杯，把双手举向空中
This is the World Cup, put the flags up in the air
这就是世界杯，把旗帜举向空中
This is the World Cup, everybody come and cheer
这就是世界杯，大家都来欢呼
And stand up, and stand up, if you ain't got no fear
站起来，站起来，只要你无所畏惧
This is the World Cup, this is the World Cup
这就是世界杯，这就是世界杯